<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
<idinfo>
<descript>
<abstract>This layer features trailheads in Rocky Mountain National Park. The layers attribute table includes a basic parking field. For more information about park fees, visit: https://www.nps.gov/romo/planyourvisit/fees.htm</abstract>
<purpose>Trailheads in Rocky Mountain National Park</purpose>
</descript>
<keywords>
<theme>
<themekt>None</themekt>
<themekey>NPS</themekey>
<themekey>IMR</themekey>
<themekey>ROMO</themekey>
<themekey>Rocky Mountain</themekey>
<themekey>National Park</themekey>
<themekey>Trail</themekey>
<themekey>Hiking</themekey>
<themekey>Hike</themekey>
<themekey>Trailhead</themekey>
<themekey>Transportation</themekey>
</theme>
</keywords>
<accconst>None</accconst>
<useconst>The National Park Service shall not be held liable for improper or incorrect use of the data described and/or contained herein. These data and related graphics (i.e. GIF or JPG format files) are not legal documents and are not intended to be used as such. The information contained in these data is dynamic and may change over time. The data are not better than the original sources from which they were derived. It is the responsibility of the data user to use the data appropriately and consistent within the limitations of geospatial data in general and these data in particular. The related graphics are intended to aid the data user in acquiring relevant data; it is not appropriate to use the related graphics as data. The National Park Service gives no warranty, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of these data. It is strongly recommended that these data are directly acquired from an NPS server and not indirectly through other sources which may have changed the data in some way. Although these data have been processed successfully on computer systems at the National Park Service, no warranty expressed or implied is made regarding the utility of the data on other systems for general or scientific purposes, nor shall the act of distribution constitute any such warranty. This disclaimer applies both to individual use of the data and aggregate use with other data.Commercial entities using these data for Location Based Service, map publication, or other redistribution of these data should thoroughly read the contents of this metadata. Improper application of these data by failure to do so could result in inappropriate use of these data, including, but not limited to, errors in navigation resulting in hazardous conditions, for which the National Park Service is not liable.</useconst>
<datacred>Rocky Mountain National Park</datacred>
</idinfo>
<metainfo>
<metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
<metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
<mettc>local time</mettc>
</metainfo>
</metadata>
